infinity-tracking.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy

Infinity Tracking Limited ("Infinity") is committed to protecting your personal data. This privacy policy will inform you how we look after your personal data we collect from you when you visit our website (regardless of where you visit it from), or that you provide to us and will tell you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you. By visiting our website, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

### Purpose of this Privacy Policy

This privacy policy aims to give you information on how we collect and process your personal data through your use of this website, including any data you may provide through this website when you sign up to our newsletter, contact us, purchase a product or service or any other interaction etc.

This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.

It is important that you read this privacy policy together with any other privacy policy or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy policy supplements any such other notices and is not intended to override them.

Infinity is the data controller of the personal information that we hold about you. Infinity complies with the requirements of the law and is registered with the Information Commissioner's Office.

If you have any questions about this privacy notice, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact the data privacy manager using the details set out below.

**Full name of legal entity:** Infinity Tracking Limited  
**Name or title of person to contact:** Data Protection Officer  
**Email address:** legal@infinity.co  
**Telephone number:** 0808 2502 999  
**Postal address:** London Court, 39 London Road, Reigate, Surrey, RH2 9AQ 

You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance.

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. Personal data or personal information means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data) (this includes information relating to your name, email address, or other identifiers relating to you such as cookies).

This policy explains how we collect, use and store the personal information you provide to us when you use our service or website.

We will only use personal in accordance with the content of this policy, as amended from time to time.

### What we collect

We will collect and process the following data about you:

**Information you give us.** This is information about you that you give us when you create an account, complete forms on our website or correspond with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. It includes information you provide when you register to use our site, subscribe to our services and when you report a problem with our site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial or credit card information etc.

**Information we collect about you:**

We automatically collect certain information when you use our website and services. In order to manage the service Infinity stores, maintains and processes information relating to your service and account, including:

  * retaining information about your contract and other information relating to your account;
  * call tracking activity information including: call duration, inbound caller line identification (i.e. the phone number calling you), call forwarding information, call data/time and duration, and other information required to generate calling reports for your records and our billing purposes;
  * recording calls and retaining the call recording unless you request us to disable call recording; and,

We also record information when you use our website relating to:

  * technical information: including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information and browser type and version;
  * information about your visit: including account activity, clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time) and login information;
  * Identity Data includes first name, last name, username or similar identifier, title;
  * Contact Data includes billing address, email address and telephone numbers;
  * Financial Data includes bank account and payment card details;
  * Profile Data includes your username and password, purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses;
  * Usage Data includes information about how you use our website, products and services; and
  * Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

### How is your personal data collected?

We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:

  * **Direct interactions**.  
You may give us your Identity, Contact and Financial Data by filling in forms or by corresponding with us by post, phone, email or otherwise. This includes personal data you provide when you: 
    * apply for our products or services;
    * create an account on our website;
    * subscribe to our service or publications;
    * request marketing to be sent to you;
    * enter a competition, promotion or survey; or
    * give us some feedback.
  * **Automated technologies or interactions**.  
As you interact with our website, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies. We may also receive Technical Data about you if you visit other websites employing our cookies. Please see our cookie policy below for further details. 
  * **Third parties or publicly available sources**.  
We may receive personal data about you from various third parties and public sources as set out below: 
    * Technical Data from the following parties: 
      1. analytics providers such as Google based outside the EU;
      2. advertising networks; and
      3. search information providers.
    * Contact, Financial and Transaction Data from providers of technical, payment and delivery services.
    * Identity and Contact Data from data brokers or aggregators.
    * Identity and Contact Data from publicly availably sources such as Companies House and the Electoral Register based inside the EU.

### What we do with the information we gather

We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:

  * **Information you give to us**.  
We will use this information: 
    * where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you and to provide you with the information and services that you request from us;
    * to respond to an inquiry or support matter initiated by you;
    * depending on your marketing preferences, we may provide you with information about other services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;
    * to notify you (in accordance with your marketing preferences) about notifications, updates or changes to your service or account; or
    * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * **Information we collect**.  
We will use this information: 
    * to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
    * to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
    * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so; or
    * as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure.

### Purposes for which we will use your personal data

We have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.

Note that we may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please contact us if you need details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one ground has been set out in the table below.

Purpose/Activity | Type of data | Lawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interest  
---|---|---  
To register you as a new customer |  (a) Identity  
(b) Contact  | Performance of a contract with you  
To process and deliver your order including:  
(a) Manage payments, fees and charges  
(b) Collect and recover money owed to us  |  (a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Financial  
(d) Transaction  
(e) Marketing and Communications  |  (a) Performance of a contract with you  
(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to recover debts due to us)   
To manage our relationship with you which will include:  
(a) Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy  
(b) Asking you to leave a review or take a survey  |  (a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Profile  
(d) Marketing and Communications  |  (a) Performance of a contract with you  
(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation  
(c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how customers use our products/services)   
To enable you to partake in a prize draw, competition or complete a survey  |  (a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Profile  
(d) Usage  
(e) Marketing and Communications  |  (a) Performance of a contract with you  
(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them and grow our business)   
To administer and protect our business and this website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data)  |  (a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Technical  |  (a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise)  
(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation   
To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you  |  (a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Profile  
(d) Usage  
(e) Marketing and Communications  
(f) Technical  |  Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy)   
To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences  |  (a) Technical  
(b) Usage  |  Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy)   
To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you  |  (a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Technical  
(d) Usage  
(e) Profile  |  Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business)   
  
### Marketing

We strive to provide you with choices regarding certain personal data uses, particularly around marketing and advertising. We have established the following personal data control mechanisms:

**Promotional Offers From Us**

We may use your Identity, Contact, Technical, Usage and Profile Data to form a view on what we think you may want or need, or what may be of interest to you. This is how we decide which products, services and offers may be relevant for you (we call this marketing).

You will receive marketing communications from us if you have requested information from us or purchased goods or services from us or if you provided us with your details when you entered a competition or registered for a promotion and, in each case, you have not opted out of receiving that marketing.

**Third-Party Marketing**

We will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any company outside the Infinity group of companies for marketing purposes.

**Opting Out**

You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by Contacting us at any time.

Where you opt out of receiving these marketing messages, this will not apply to personal data provided to us as a result of a product/service purchase, warranty registration, product/service experience or other transactions.

### How we use cookies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website and to improve your experience on the website. In this section of the policy you will find out what cookies are, how we use them and how you can switch them off.

However, for the best experience on our website, we would recommend that you enable cookies in your web browser as disabling our cookies may mean that not all the functions on the website can work properly.

**What is a cookie?**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added, and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. By continuing to browse this site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.

**What cookies do we use?**

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

**How to control or delete cookies**

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, for the best experience on our website, we would recommend that you enable cookies in your web browser as disabling our cookies may mean that not all the functions on the website can work properly.

### Disclosure of your information

We may have to share your personal data if one of these situations occur:

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to comply with our regulatory obligations. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

If Infinity or a substantial part of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

### International transfers

We share your personal data within the Infinity group. This will involve transferring your data outside the European Economic Area (EEA).

Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded. Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US. For further details, see European Commission: EU-US Privacy Shield.

Please contact us if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data out of the EEA.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. To prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in unauthorised way, altered or disclosed, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We will also notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

### Data retention

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Changes to privacy policy

This version was last updated on May 1st, 2018 and historic versions can be obtained by contacting us.

We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.

If we need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.

Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.

### Your legal rights

Under certain circumstances, you will have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data.

For example, you have rights to:

  * Request access to your personal data;
  * Request correction of your personal data;
  * Request erasure of your personal data;
  * Object to processing of your personal data;
  * Request restriction of processing your personal data;
  * Request transfer of your personal data; and
  * Withdraw consent.

If you wish to exercise any of the rights, please contact us at London Court, 39 London Road, Reigate, Surrey, RH2 9AQ, UK or legal@infinity.co

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances. If you would like a copy of the information held please write to us at the above address

If you also believe that any information we are holding is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
